

- (510)-519-6638
- www.melissazandman.com
- hello@melissazandman.com

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Software Engineer Bootcamp Nucamp 2020

Software Engineer Fellowship Hackbright Academy 2019

Industrial Engineering Instituto Tecnologico de Ciudad Madero 2008-2012

SKILLS

HTML

CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind Flask, jQuery, Jinja Javascript (AJAX,JSON) React JS, React Native Python, NodeJS, Express MongoDB, SQL PostgreSQL

Git, GitHub, Bash (Command Line)

Figma

Wordpress

Shopify

MELISSA ZANDMAN

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Versatile web developer with a flair for visual design. Moved from Mexico to California in 2018 to transition from industrial engineering to software engineering. Excited to join your team to deliver impactful and delightful web solutions that prioritize user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Client Success & Operations

Countable, San Francisco, CA I January 2022 - November 2023

- Reduced site development time by 79%, from 36.8 business days to 7.6 business days.
- Successfully launched over 15 client "impact" sites with meticulous attention to detail and high client satisfaction.
- Translated detailed Figma mocks into pixel-perfect implementations.
- Demonstrated expertise in HTML and CSS, and delivering responsive and visually-appealing websites.
- Proactively addressed change requests from clients, providing efficient solutions
- Supported team members in overcoming challenges and fostering a collaborative work environment.
- Recognized for meeting tight deadlines and exceeding performance expectations.
- Gained exposure to Agile/Scrum methodologies and JavaScript framework
- Initiated and developed a comprehensive Figma template, enabling seamless site creation for the team despite the absence of a dedicated product designer.

Solutions Engineer

Lenos Software, San Francisco I December 2020 - January 2022

- Identified feature requests and documentation gaps, enhancing support
- Developed customized solutions, leading to a 15% increase in customer retention.
- Established strong cross-functional relationships with product management, sales and marketing, and engineering.